Hey!
Hang in there!
Hey, you hear me?!
No...
What...
What the hell are you?!
What the...
What in the world?
What happened here? Tell me!
A... A horde of monsters...
No way.
We must tell the tribal chief.
The Forest of Ente
Very good. Maintain your posture
and be aware of your core balance.
'Kay.
Don't swing thoughtlessly.
It will leave you wide open.
Okay, another 30 swings!
Okay!
Dolan.
Would you like to join the academy?
If you want to protect the village you love,
leaving it might be one way to do it.
I suppose so...
Will Dolan leave me behind
and go far away someday?
Why, you!
I'm happy that Celina is steadily
becoming a part of this village.
Long may these times continue.
Dolan, I have a favor to ask.
I would like to explore the forest.
Why the forest?
Well, I hear there are many
vicious animals here,
and I wish to test my mettle against them.
The forest is dangerous.
It's not worth venturing into
without a solid reason.
I do have a reason.
Albert says he hasn't been able
to take his pigs grazing.
He could find their favorite acorns
aplenty in the forest, could he not?
So, you want to guard the
pigs while they graze?
I believe helping the village is
reason enough. Do you disagree?
That sure is a lot of armor.
Right. There have been sightings of beasts
that normally don't venture out here.
So they're being extra careful.
Though with Celina, Chris, and me here,
there shouldn't be all that
much cause for concern.
The air in the forest is so fresh.
Nature truly is healing.
You can say that again!
We'll be over there.
Right. Take care.
Not many people come through here.
Stay alert.
Sir!
Get back here!
Don't wander off!
A... A bladed tiger!
Stay on your toes! You never
know when animals will pounce!
What?
That's Balan's voice!
Wait!
S-Stay away.
Balan!
Energy Bolt!
What kind of monster is that?
That's no monster.
It's a dweller of the
demonic realm, a demon.
A demon?!
This one is a lower-ranked demon, a scout.
I believe they were called zerts.
Lower-ranked or not,
they're still very agile and powerful.
How do you know this?
I read about them in a book
at old Maguru's place.
I'll keep it pinned down. You take it out.
Got it.
I beseech thee, O laws of power.
Give me an arrow to smite my foe.
Energy Bolt!
What just happened?
Chris, please don't tell the
villagers about the demon.
Elder, how is Captain Balan doing?
No threat to his life, it seems.
Maguru and Miu are taking care of him now.
I see.
Thank goodness.
A bladed tiger is rare enough,
but they say there was an
unknown monster, too?
That's bad news.
Do monsters like that appear
frequently around here?
No, this is the first I've of
heard of anything like it.
Balan is the leader of our village's
garrison and the strongest soldier here.
And if even he was hurt that
badly by this monster...
Yeah, even a bladed tiger
would be big news here,
but that demon is the bigger issue.
What's going on in that forest?
Maguru?
Balan has come to.
He should be fine now.
He wasn't cut by a bladed tiger.
That was a much more potent slash.
It couldn't have been any ordinary animal.
Master, is something strange
happening in the forest?
If it is, I'll go—
Dolan.
Even if it is so, we must
learn to live with it.
Such is life in the frontier.
We live in harmony with nature
and return to it at the end.
Do you understand?
I do, but defying nature
is also the human way.
Master, please let me go
investigate the forest.
Dolan...
I'll yield.
However, you must not go alone.
Take someone with you, just in case.
Then I'll go.
Absolutely not.
But why?
What would we ever tell the academy
if something happened to you?
We even promised Commissioner Gouda
we'd keep you safe just the other day.
Still...
I'll go!
I'll accompany Dolan into the forest.
I have my cursed eyes, and I can use magic.
I'm sure I can be of some help.
Er...
You're okay with that, right?!
Let Celina and me investigate the forest.
Chris, this is our village.
We will sort our problems out ourselves.
Very well. You and the
young lady can handle it.
However, I want you to prioritize
your own lives above all else.
If you can't promise to come back
alive and safe, the deal is off.
We will return perfectly unharmed.
I promise you that.
It's been a while since we've had
time to ourselves, hasn't it?
Huh? Y-Yeah, it has.
Get it together! I can't get distracted
by the fact that we're alone!
I must show Dolan that
I can be useful in battle!
I'll try my best not to be a burden.
That's very reassuring.
And we have your cursed eyes
if it comes down to it.
Oh, I forgot to cast them on you.
Don't joke about that.
Er...
Good morning. It's a fine day, isn't it?
I just happened to be in the
mood for a forest stroll, too.
Chris?
Didn't the elder forbid you
from leaving the village?
I thought you had accepted his decision.
You said you'd sort out your
village's problems yourselves.
But Verun Village is a place that
I'm starting to care very much about, too.
Is it so strange that I wish to
help the people who I hold dear?
I see.
What do you think, Celina?
Huh?
Hm... I don't see any problem with it.
I feel the same way as her.
The village's problems
are our problems, too.
Very well.
Let's just say we happened to
be going in the same direction.
I'm glad that you two are so understanding.
They feel the same way, huh?
Is gaining more places
and people to care about
simply a part of life for
people as time goes on?
I'm starting to become quite human myself.
Another monster!
Here, have a fruit.
Huh?
"Sorry for scaring you just now"?
It's fine.
I have never seen a monster be so docile.
What am I witnessing right now?
Dolan, is she always like this?
What is even going on over there?!
I couldn't tell you why, but it
seems they've taken a liking to me.
They were so scared of me at first, too.
Okay.
Eat up!
Are you two not scared of monsters?
Come on, Christina.
I'm a monster too, you know.
O-Oh, right you are.
I completely forgot about that.
If only everyone else was like you.
Indeed.
Oh, Dolan, did Miu make that jam?
That's right. It's her latest creation.
Yay! I want some!
It's all right, Christina.
Try feeding him this.
They were simply hungry.
They must've tried to attack us
because they couldn't forage for food.
They're such powerful monsters, and they
got chased off their feeding grounds?
Those giant spotted spiders
might've been the same, too.
The change in the forest is
starting to feel very real.
Thank you.
Indeed, we cannot very well ignore
this state of affairs.
Delicious!
My mother baked those using
wheat from the village,
and my father taught me
how to dry and cure meat.
What do you say? A meal like this
is a fun experience too, is it not?
Huh...
Yes.
And I'm starting to find them
cuter the more I look at them.
Christina, you cut such a
pretty sight just eating.
I agree. She has a fascinating charm to her.
It's almost like she's straight
out of a classic art piece.
Stop teasing me.
Say, Christina, would you be willing
to tell me the secret to your charm?
Huh?
It might help boost my charm spell
and be a powerful asset in
my search for a husband.
Please teach me!
I'm not sure what to tell you.
You don't want to?
Uh...
You don't need it.
Huh?
What do you mean?
You're fine the way you are.
Huh? What?
Does he mean I'm charming enough already?
I don't need to search for a husband?
Is he going to take me for his wife?
Gosh, Dolan. He never showed any
indication that he felt this way.
What a shy boy!
I'm not sure how to respond
to this sudden proposal!
Huh?
Did you feel that?
Yes.
Run...
How unusual. It's a fairy.
Is she hurt?
Run... away...
Is she saying something?
A zert?!
Celina, send them away!
Okay!
Get away from here!
Let's do this.
Right!
There's more coming.
Right.
Dolan!
Energy Rain!
There you are.
I see. There was another
hiding in the back?
You think you've taken away my sword?
I feel bad for my parents who
gifted me this body, but...
Transform.
Yeah, my dragon powers
make things much easier.
Christina!
Jaraam!
Thanks, you saved me.
Oh, you would've been fine
even without my help.
That humility is part of what makes
you so beautiful and charming.
Wh-What are you saying, Dolan?
Me? Beautiful?
Are you okay?
You aren't hurt?
Um, thank you for helping me.
A-Are you humans?
And a lamia?
That's right. I'm Dolan.
This is Christina...
And I'm Celina.
I'm Merl.
That demon soldier started
chasing me out of nowhere.
I see. Those troops must be the ones
behind the change in the forest.
The zert are mere scouts.
There must be more powerful demons coming.
Merl, could you tell us what is happening?
We're here to investigate
the change in the forest.
We can help you.
Erm, well...
We're in a lot of trouble,
so I really appreciate your offer, but...
"We"? Hm?
We're surrounded.
Seems so.
Demons? No.
They're looking at us with caution
and suspicion, not hostility.
Which means...
Dolan?
Wood elves.
Yeah.
Merl, get away from them and come here.
Next Episode
This week's lucky item is jam!
Look forward to next time!